prowrestlingtees.com 2019-06-23

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
    This privacy policy sets out how ProWrestlingTees.com (“we”, “us”, or “ProWrestlingTees.com”) uses and protects any information we obtain from your use of the ProWrestlingTees.com website (the “Website”). ProWrestlingTees.com is committed to protecting your privacy. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using the Website, such information will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. ProWrestlingTees.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you agree with the most current Privacy Policy. Your access of the Website constitutes your acceptance of these terms.
  
What We Collect
    We may request that you provide the following information (“Submitted Data”): name, contact information including email address, demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests, other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers. We also use web tracking software to collect the name of the domain from which you access the Internet, identify the name of the website from which you linked to ProWrestingTees.com, data regarding your operating system, browser type, device type, screen resolution, IP address and other technical information, your usage of our website, and session information as you interact with our website (“Collected Data”). For the exhaustive list of cookies we collect see the List of Cookies We Collect section.
  
What we do with the information we gather
    We use Collected Data to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for Internal record keeping. We may use your personal information for our everyday business purposes such as service improvements, security, payment processing, analytics, operations, fraud detection and prevention, reporting, making back-ups and legal compliance. We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests. To best serve you, we may share your personal information with other members of the Pro Wrestling Tees family of companies and with third parties that provide us with support services or that help us market our products and services, administer our programs, operations, fulfill your requests, surveys, contests, or sweepstakes and product reviews. We may also disclose your personal information when we have reason to believe that it is necessary to identify you, contact you, manage information security or bring legal action to protect your rights or the rights of Creative Ventures, Inc. or others. We may also disclose your personal information when you ask us to do so or when we believe it is required or permitted by law. Certain browsers have settings that allow you to turn on a "do not track" feature. This Website does not currently support “do not track” and will not honor your web browser's “do not track” signal.

Subject to the usage by the third party service providers as discussed above, we do not participate in tracking networks and do not intentionally or knowingly allow other parties to collect personally-identifiable information about your on-line activities over time and across different websites, when you visit the sites or use any of the services. We do not, however, have control over third parties’ activities, including if a third party accesses information based on your visit to our website. You should review the Privacy Policies and Terms of Service for any third-party websites you visit to ensure you agree with their treatment of your information.

Security
    We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
  
How we use cookies
    Our store uses the data we collect for three basic purposes: to operate our business and provide (including improving and personalizing) the services we offer, to send communications, including promotional communications, and to display advertising. In carrying out these purposes, we combine data we collect through the various store services you use to give you a more seamless, consistent and personalized experience. However, to enhance privacy, we have built in technological and procedural safeguards designed to prevent certain data combinations. For example, we store data we collect from you when you are unauthenticated (not signed in) separately from any account information that directly identifies you, such as your name, email address or phone number.
  
Sharing Your Information
    A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets us know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie does not give us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

Links to other websites
    Our Website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
  
Controlling your personal information
    Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the Website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes. If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at info@prowrestlingtees.com. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us at info@prowrestlingtees.com or 2348 N. Damen Ave., Chicago, Illinois 60647. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
  
Management of personal data
    You can view or edit your personal data online for many of our services. You can also make choices about our collection and use of your data. How you can access or control your personal data will depend on which services you use. You can choose whether you wish to receive promotional communications from our store by email, SMS, physical mail, and telephone. If you receive promotional email or SMS messages from us and would like to opt out, you can do so by following the directions in that message. You can also make choices about the receipt of promotional email, telephone calls, and postal mail by visiting and signing into Company Promotional Communications Manager, which allows you to update contact information, manage contact preferences, opt out of email subscriptions, and choose whether to share your contact information with our partners. These choices do not apply to mandatory service communications that are part of certain store services.
  
Illinois Privacy Rights
    Illinois law entitles residents to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal information we share with third parties or with corporate affiliates for those entities’ direct marketing purposes. We do not provide any personal information to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. If you want to request a notice or have any questions about our privacy practices, please contact us at info@prowrestlingtees.com.
  
Changes to Privacy Policy
    This Privacy Policy is effective as of November 1st, 2015. We may change this Policy from time to time. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this Website so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and to whom we may disclose it.
